( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
This is evidence of Xia Shang running illegal businesses.
هذا دليل على أن شيا شانغ يدير أعمالاً غير قانونية.
Give it to the police.
سلمه للشرطة.
Now.
الآن.
When you feel unwell next time,
عندما تشعر بتوعك في المرة القادمة،
just tell me.
أخبرني فقط.
Go out.
الخروج.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Why did you lose control again?
لماذا فقدت السيطرة مرة أخرى؟
Go out first.
اخرج أولاً.
I just need a moment.
أحتاج فقط إلى لحظة.
Didn't we agree last night
ألم نتفق الليلة الماضية؟
to be honest with each other?
أن نكون صادقين مع بعضنا البعض؟
If you want me to help you calm down,
إذا كنت تريدني أن أساعدك على الهدوء،
just tell me.
أخبرني فقط.
I want.
أريد.
Why is he taking medication for anxiety?
لماذا يتناول أدوية لعلاج القلق؟
Does it have anything to do with the injuries on his arm?
هل للأمر علاقة بالإصابات التي لحقت بذراعه؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I only wanted to hold you for a while
أردت فقط أن أحتضنك لبعض الوقت
last night.
ليلة أمس.
I didn't have any other bad intentions.
لم تكن لدي أي نوايا سيئة أخرى.
But the fact is,
لكن الحقيقة هي،
we slept in the same bed all night.
نمنا في نفس السرير طوال الليل.
It's hard for me to believe you had no bad intentions.
يصعب عليّ تصديق أنك لم تكن لديك نوايا سيئة.
You have no idea
ليس لديك أدنى فكرة
you were...
كنتَ...
Let me check if you're hurt.
دعني أتأكد مما إذا كنت مصابًا.
You don't have to be nervous.
لا داعي للتوتر.
You only held me for a bit last night.
لم تحتضنني إلا لفترة قصيرة الليلة الماضية.
Nothing else happened.
لم يحدث شيء آخر.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
have you been losing control often these past two years?
هل فقدت السيطرة على نفسك كثيراً خلال العامين الماضيين؟
Two...
اثنين...
Two or three times.
مرتين أو ثلاث مرات.
What about the injuries on your arm?
ماذا عن الإصابات التي لحقت بذراعك؟
And the medicine under your pillow.
والدواء تحت وسادتك.
When did you start taking it?
متى بدأت بتناوله؟
Two years ago.
قبل عامين.
After you left.
بعد مغادرتك.
You know how it is.
أنت تعرف كيف تسير الأمور.
When a Ren is separated from their Yin too long,
عندما ينفصل عنصر الرين عن عنصر الين لفترة طويلة جدًا،
they usually develop
عادة ما تتطور
separation anxiety.
قلق الانفصال.
When it gets really bad,
عندما تسوء الأمور حقاً،
I can't control myself
لا أستطيع السيطرة على نفسي
and end up scratching myself.
وينتهي بي الأمر بحك نفسي.
Luckily,
لحسن الحظ،
we're close to finishing the medicine.
نحن على وشك الانتهاء من تحضير الدواء.
Mr. Ding already had Lin Juan
كان السيد دينغ قد حصل بالفعل على لين جوان
and two volunteers test it.
ويقوم متطوعان باختباره.
If the drug works well,
إذا كان الدواء فعالاً،
you won't have to suffer like this anymore.
لن تضطر إلى المعاناة بهذه الطريقة بعد الآن.
After taking the medicine,
بعد تناول الدواء،
can I pursue you as a normal person?
هل يمكنني أن ألاحقك كشخص عادي؟
That's your business.
هذا هو عملك
You don't need to ask me.
لستَ بحاجةٍ لسؤالي.
Yesterday's blood test results are out.
نتائج فحص الدم الذي أجريت أمس قد صدرت.
Our medicine
أدويتنا
worked!
نجح الأمر!
Yesterday's volunteers,
متطوعو الأمس،
whether Yin or Ren,
سواء كان يين أو رين،
now have no detectable Affinity virus in their bodies.
لم يعد لديهم أي فيروس أفينيتي قابل للكشف في أجسامهم.
I'll file a report and contact the authorities,
سأقدم بلاغاً وأتصل بالسلطات.
try to get
حاول الحصول على
fast-track approval,
الموافقة السريعة،
so the medicine can go on the market as soon as possible.
حتى يتمكن الدواء من طرحه في السوق في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Let's wait a bit longer.
لننتظر قليلاً.
Logically,
منطقياً،
we still need more observation
ما زلنا بحاجة إلى مزيد من المراقبة
of the test subjects' physical condition.
فيما يتعلق بالحالة البدنية للأشخاص الخاضعين للاختبار.
You can wait,
يمكنك الانتظار،
but many people can't.
لكن الكثير من الناس لا يستطيعون ذلك.
Lives are at stake.
الأرواح في خطر.
We must get this medicine to market as soon as possible.
يجب أن نطرح هذا الدواء في السوق في أسرع وقت ممكن.
I'm heading out first.
سأخرج أولاً.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
The formula looks off.
تبدو الصيغة غير صحيحة.
Where are the fragments?
أين الشظايا؟
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Something was left out.
تم إغفال شيء ما.
Who logged the device data?
من قام بتسجيل بيانات الجهاز؟
Mr. Ding.
السيد دينغ.
No.
لا.
We need to notify the volunteers immediately.
علينا إبلاغ المتطوعين فوراً.
There's something wrong with the medicine.
هناك خطأ ما في الدواء.
Tell them to go to the hospital right away.
أخبرهم أن يذهبوا إلى المستشفى فوراً.
I haven't been able to reach them all day.
لم أتمكن من الوصول إليهم طوال اليوم.
We'll emergency halt the drug's market launch process
سنوقف بشكل طارئ عملية طرح الدواء في السوق
before we find a way to locate Lin Juan and the others.
قبل أن نجد طريقة لتحديد مكان لين جوان والآخرين.
Okay.
تمام.
No signal.
لا توجد إشارة.
Sorry.
آسف.
I forgot to mention earlier.
نسيت أن أذكر ذلك سابقاً.
This house
هذا المنزل
has a signal jammer installed.
تم تركيب جهاز تشويش على الإشارات.
Don't be nervous.
لا تكن عصبيا.
We've accomplished something great and difficult together.
لقد أنجزنا معًا شيئًا عظيمًا وصعبًا.
Let's celebrate with a meal.
فلنحتفل بتناول وجبة.
You've both put in a lot of work
لقد بذلتما الكثير من الجهد
over this period.
خلال هذه الفترة.
You may
يمكنك
just get some good rest.
احصل على قسط جيد من الراحة.
I've submitted the lab reports and the formula.
لقد قدمت تقارير المختبر والصيغة.
If things go smoothly,
إذا سارت الأمور على ما يرام،
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
within 24 hours,
خلال 24 ساعة،
it can go into mass production
يمكن أن ينتقل إلى الإنتاج الضخم
and enter the market.
ودخول السوق.
But there's a problem with that medicine.
لكن هناك مشكلة في هذا الدواء.
After taking it,
بعد تناوله،
it's not just the virus that disappears, right?
الأمر لا يقتصر على اختفاء الفيروس فقط، أليس كذلك؟
Right.
يمين.
There's also coma
وهناك أيضاً الغيبوبة
and organ failure.
وفشل الأعضاء.
The person dies
يموت الشخص
without much pain.
بدون ألم يُذكر.
So
لذا
your goal was never to save people.
لم يكن هدفك أبدًا إنقاذ الناس.
It was to kill them.
كان الهدف هو قتلهم.
The result doesn't matter.
النتيجة لا تهم.
Our original intention is the same.
كانت نيتنا الأصلية هي نفسها.
To eliminate the virus.
للقضاء على الفيروس.
Now the medicine is done.
انتهى العلاج الآن.
Our years of effort weren't wasted.
لم تذهب جهودنا التي بذلناها على مر السنين سدى.
Let's celebrate.
فلنحتفل.
♪But wrote it in the sand...♪
♪لكنها كُتبت على الرمال...♪
You popped the champagne too early.
لقد فتحت زجاجة الشمبانيا مبكراً جداً.
This isn't what we agreed on.
هذا ليس ما اتفقنا عليه.
So now,
والآن،
fill in the part of the formula you deliberately left out,
أكمل الجزء من الصيغة الذي أغفلته عمداً،
redevelop the medicine,
إعادة تطوير الدواء،
and set everything back on track.
وأعاد كل شيء إلى مساره الصحيح.
Xu,
شو،
you still don't understand.
ما زلت لا تفهم.
We have gone as far as we can
لقد وصلنا إلى أقصى ما يمكننا
with this drug's development.
مع تطور هذا الدواء.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
The part I "erased"
الجزء الذي "محوته"
never existed in the first place.
لم تكن موجودة أصلاً.
This is my second time
هذه هي المرة الثانية التي أزور فيها هذا المكان.
developing the medicine.
تطوير الدواء.
The last time I searched for a formula
آخر مرة بحثت فيها عن صيغة
was sixteen years ago.
كان ذلك قبل ستة عشر عاماً.
Back then, my name was
في ذلك الوقت، كان اسمي
Wu Ming.
وو مينغ.
I had a son and a daughter.
كان لدي ابن وابنة.
My son was called Wu Siyuan.
كان اسم ابني وو سييوان.
My daughter was called
تم استدعاء ابنتي
Wu Nongyu.
وو نونجيو.
They had a wonderful mother.
كانت لديهم أم رائعة.
Yu.
يو.
She devoted her whole life
كرست حياتها كلها
to developing a drug
تطوير دواء
that could eliminate the Affinity virus.
هذا من شأنه أن يقضي على فيروس أفينيتي.
But my research field was different from hers.
لكن مجال بحثي كان مختلفاً عن مجالها.
The help I could offer was very limited.
كانت المساعدة التي أستطيع تقديمها محدودة للغاية.
After years of research,
بعد سنوات من البحث،
she and her assistant, Dayu,
هي ومساعدتها، دايو،
finally developed a formula.
وأخيراً توصلنا إلى صيغة.
Ms. Lin,
السيدة لين،
I've found almost all the components
لقد وجدت جميع المكونات تقريباً
in your formula.
في معادلتك.
Only one ingredient is missing as a catalyst.
ينقصنا عنصر واحد فقط كمحفز.
I can't find a suitable one.
لا أستطيع العثور على واحد مناسب.
Tell me the properties of that ingredient.
أخبرني بخصائص هذا المكون.
I'll ask colleagues at other institutes.
سأسأل زملائي في معاهد أخرى.
We've solved the hardest problems.
لقد حللنا أصعب المشاكل.
A couple more days won't make a difference, right?
بضعة أيام إضافية لن تُحدث فرقاً، أليس كذلك؟
Time is the one thing we have plenty of.
الوقت هو الشيء الوحيد الذي نملك منه الكثير.
She made the first-generation drug
لقد صنعت الجيل الأول من الأدوية
without the final ingredient
بدون المكون الأخير
and didn't tell me.
ولم يخبرني.
Then she volunteered to test it on herself.
ثم تطوعت لتجربته على نفسها.
She fell into a coma.
دخلت في غيبوبة.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪